A few days later
Несколько дней спустя
The Son of Heaven's edict arrives
пришёл указ императора
While pardoning you
тебя помиловали сняв все обвинения
Orders the traitor Chu Huan
а изменника Чу Хуана
To be executed according to law
повелели казнить по закону
That same year
В тот же год
Prince of Ning Sikong Zheng
принц Нинь Сыкун Чжэн
Is enfeoffed as Crown Prince
был назначен наследным принцем
Chancellor Chen Dao
а канцлер Чэнь Дао
Also serves as Eastern Palace Grand Tutor
получил звание наставника наследника
The surge of succession struggle
Борьба за трон
Seems to have calmed
казалось бы утихла
Under Prince of Ning's strict guard
Под надзором принца Ниня
You can only in remote lands
тебе пришлось жить в уединении на окраинах империи
Watch from afar the calm waters
глядя на спокойные воды
As a carefree prince fishing and playing with dogs
оставаясь праздным князем забавляющимся рыбалкой и собаками
Wei Kingdom unifies the north in one move
Вэй объединяет север
And marches south
и двигается на юг
I heard
Говорят
The order calling you to aid
приказ вызвать тебя на подмогу
Is already on its way
уже в пути
I know you want to return
Я знаю ты хочешь вернуться
These years
Ты столько лет
You've worked hard to build the border army
выстраивал армию на границе
And there are still some in court who favor you
в столице ещё остались сторонники
But once you show yourself
но если ты проявишь себя
If you lose, you'll be crushed to pieces
и проиграешь ты погибнешь
What will happen to me and the child then?
а что тогда будет со мной и нашим ребёнком